(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-17T18:05:51.815190",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
Grimoire 4♥Ever ～ 四人で綴られ、永遠に残る魔導書 ～
Grimoire 4♥Ever ~ A grimoire woven by four, remaining eternal ~
君に届け 星のメロディー
Reach you, the melody of stars
想いを ギュッと ギュッと 詰め込んで
Packing our feelings tight, so tight
君と 奏でる この ハーモニー
Playing this harmony with you
これからも ずっと 続いてく
Continuing on forever from now on
ねえ ねえ もっと 近くにおいでよ
Hey, hey, come a little closer
回り始めた 世界で踊らない？ 終わらない
Won't you dance in this world that started turning? It won't end
わくわく 魔法かけたら
If you cast a thrilling magic spell
ドキドキは sync してほら party time 止まらない
Hearts sync up, look, party time won't stop
twinkle twinkle little stars
願いを 込めて
Putting our wishes into them
twinkle twinkle 夜空で歌いましょう
Twinkle, twinkle, let's sing in the night sky
君に 響け 星のメロディー
Resonate to you, the melody of stars
新しい 星座を描いて
Drawing a new constellation
君と 繋がっている この宇宙に 宝石を 散りばめよう
Scattering jewels across this sky connected to you
君に届け 星のメロディー
Reach you, the melody of stars
想いを ギュッと ギュッと 詰め込んで
Packing our feelings tight, so tight
君と 奏でる この ハーモニー
Playing this harmony with you
これからも ずっと 続いてく
Continuing on forever from now on
clap clap ほら 一緒に 鳴らそう
Clap clap, hey, let's ring it together
この 瞬間を キャッチして 忘れない stary night
Catching this moment, an unforgettable starry night
キラキラ 魔法 解けても
Even if the sparkly magic fades
胸に 締まった ドキメキは 消えない 止まらない
The excitement locked in our hearts won't fade, won't stop
twinkle twinkle little stars
願いを 込めて
Putting our wishes into them
twinkle twinkle 夜空で踊りましょう
Twinkle, twinkle, let's dance in the night sky
twinkle 4 you
Twinkle for you
君と 残す 星のメモリー
The memory of stars left with you
想い出 ギュッと ギュッと 詰め込んで
Packing our memories tight, so tight...
君と出会えた この素敵な奇跡と夢を
The wonderful miracle and dream of meeting you
また叶えよう
Let's make them come true once again.
君に届け 星のメロディー
Reaching you, the star's melody,
新しい星座を描いて
Drawing a brand new constellation,
君と繋がっている この宇宙(そら)に
Into this cosmos connected with you,
宝石を散りばめよう
Let's scatter jewels across the sky.
君に届け 星のメロディー
Reaching you, the star's melody,
思いをギュッと ギュッと詰め込んで
Packing our feelings tightly inside,
君と奏でる このハーモニー
This harmony we play together with you,
これからもずっと続いてく
Will continue on forever from now on.
La La La...
イェーイ！
Yay!
おつぽらー！ おつらみ！
Otsupola! Otsurami!
と言うわけで皆さん！ねぽらぼ6周年記念ライブへお越しいただきありがとうございます！
And with that, everyone! Thank you so much for coming to the NePoLaBo 6th Anniversary Live!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you so much!
改めまして、ねぽらぼでーす！
Once again, we are NePoLaBo!
イェーイ！
Yay!
というわけで簡単な自己紹介、ねねからどうぞ！
Now then, for brief self-introductions, starting with Nene! Go ahead!
はーい！ホロライブ5期生、オレンジの魔法、ピンクのももじり、みんなのエナジードリンク、桃鈴ねねでーす！
Hii! Hololive 5th Gen, orange magic, pink peach rear, everyone's energy drink, Momosuzu Nene!
ありがとうございまーす！
Thank you very much!
はーい、ポルカです。ポルカおるか？おるよー！
Hi, Polka here. Is Polka here? Polka is here!
赤色の魔法であってんのか？うん、うん。はい、ポルカです。よろしくお願いします！
Red magic... is that right? Yeah, yeah. Hi, Polka here. Nice to meet you!
よろしくお願いします！
Nice to meet you!
はーい！ホロライブの、かほが肝臓、雪花ラミィです！青色の魔法です。肝臓の魔法…肝臓の魔法？
Hii! Hololive's... kaho is liver, Yukihana Lamy! Blue magic. Liver magic... liver magic?
肝臓の魔法じゃない！
Not liver magic!
はい、じゃあねぽらぼのーぼ、黒魔道士獅白ボタンです！
Hi, then NePoLaBo's "bo", black mage Shishiro Botan!
黒魔道士ね！この世の全てを滅ぼし…今回の配信のハッシュタグは、こちら！
Black mage! Destroying everything in this world... and today's stream hashtag is right here!
ハッシュタグ「ねぽらぼ6周年3Dライブ」こちらで！みなさんたくさんポストしてくださいね！
Hashtag "#NePoLaBo6thAnniversary3DLive", right here! Everyone, please post a lot!
そして、いよいよ周年ライブ始まりましたけど、どうですか皆さん？
And finally, the anniversary live has started, how do you all feel?
いやワクワクドキドキ、もうドキドキドキドキ…
Man, excited and nervous, heart pounding so much...
8月の魔法！キャッチコピーは「4人で綴られ永遠に残る魔導書」！
August's magic! The catchphrase is "A grimoire woven by four people that remains forever"!
魔法少女をイメージした帽子とステキ、ステキだね。こちらを、特別に作っていただいたました！
We had these hats and cute outfits inspired by magical girls specially made for us!
すごい！そう、これ、うちら浮いてる！宇宙だね！ねえ、浮いてる！星空に囲まれたステージで今日はライブをするんだね！
Amazing! That's right, we're floating! It's space! Hey, we're floating! We're performing on a stage surrounded by a starry sky today!
そういうことね！すごい！
Is that so! Amazing!
じゃ、みてこれ！専用の魔方陣も！わぁ、すごい！
Look at this! A dedicated magic circle too! Wow, amazing!
まぁ、そんな中でね、1曲目からみんなでちょっと魔法とかもこう、かけまくっちゃったわけですけど、どうでしたか魔法？
Well, amidst all that, starting from the first song we were casting magic everywhere, how was the magic?
えっと、まず1曲目「Twinkle 4 You」をグリムワールリミックスということで、新しくリミックスしていただきました！
Um, first, for song one, "Twinkle 4 You" as a Grimoire Remix, it was newly remixed for us!
ちょっと違ったよね、いつもと。なんかテンポ難しいとことかあるんだよね。そうそう、何回も練習したよね。
It was a bit different from usual. There are parts where the tempo is tricky, right? Yeah, we practiced so many times.
そこで魔導書に魔法で映像を投影したり、あとカストもさ、この上の方に出したりしてもらいました。そうね。この空間に、ね、魔法に頑張っていただきました！
We had magic project images onto the grimoire, and cast customs up above. That's right. In this space, magic did its best!
できるの！まあ見逃した人もいるか。ポルカたちに実はもう今回今日のためにこうやって魔法のステキも燃やし直したってことで魔法が使えるんですわ！
We can do it! Well, some people might have missed it. Polka and the others actually refired up our magic wands for today, so we can use magic!
ちょっと待ってね。やってみようかな。
Wait a minute. Let's try this.
お！お！お！
Oh! Oh! Oh!
やってみて！
Give it a try!
じゃあハートを出します。
Now, I'll summon a heart.
んーー、そ、い、そいそいそい！ほおー！
Hmm... Th-there we go! Whoa!
そういう感じ。なんかちょっ、あ、かわいいけど。
That kind of vibe. It's kinda... ah, cute though.
かわいい！かわいい！
So cute! So cute!
ハート出たね。
A heart came out.
これうちらも出せんに？
Can we put it out too?
え、やってみる？あ、じゃあ獅白行ってみよ。
Eh, want to try? Ah, then Shishiro, go ahead.
獅白せーの！
Shishiro, ready, set!
んーー、
Hmm...
はっ！
Hah!
出し方さ、そういう感じなんだ。
So that's how you summon it.
かわいい！かわいいけど、え、ラミィもやってよ。
Cute! It's cute, but, hey Lamy, you do it too.
あ、いいよ。はい！
Ah, sure. Here!
ラブちゅっ！
Love chu!
うまっ！
Yummy!
うわ、かわいい！
Whoa, cute!
うわ、でっか！
Whoa, huge!
でっかいの出たね。
A huge one came out.
えー、ラブちゅっ！ももじゅり！
Eh... Love chu! Momojuri!
早い方わかんないからつえーのこれじゃ。
It's hard to tell which is faster with this.
え、おもしろいな。すごい。
Eh, that's interesting. Amazing.
でもせっかくだからね、みんなの魔法もっと見せたいなと思うんですけど。
But since we have the chance, I want everyone to see more of our magic.
お、なんですかね？
Oh, what could it be?
まずは手始めにね、ねねが初め。
First, to start off, Nene goes first.
この空間をちょっとだけ変えたいと思います。みんな何が変わるかよく見ててね。
I want to change this space just a little bit.
Everyone watch closely to see what changes.
そんなのあるの？わかんないお前ら？
Is there something like that? You guys don't know?
んーー、えい！
Hmm... Ei!
え、でっか！大きいのきちゃった！
Eh, huge! Something huge came!
びっくりした！
I was surprised!
窓が大きくなった！
The window got bigger!
大迫力！
Such high impact!
じゃ、この窓をちょっと使ってさ、ちょっと私たちの召喚魔法を見せようじゃないですか。
Now, using this window a bit, why don't we show our summoning magic?
獅白そんなものが使えるのか？
Shishiro, can you use something like that?
いや、これはねみんなのパワーがいります。
No, this requires everyone's power.
がんばろう！
Let's do our best!
じゃあちょっと行きましょうみんな。せーの！
Then let's go, everyone. Ready, set!
うーー、えい！
Uーー, ei!
おおー！かっこいい！すげー！
Oooh! Cool! Awesome!
なんか降りてくる！うわ！
Something's coming down! Whoa!
すげー！降りてきてるー！
Awesome! It's coming down!
ありがとう！にんじん！雪民！ししろんあいこ！召喚できました！
Thank you! Carrot! Yukimin! Shishiron Aiko!
Summoned successfully!
召喚成功だ！やったね！
Summoning successful! Yay!
じゃあ一緒にね、これでみんなも集合したことだしね、みんなも連れててくれるか？
So together, since everyone's gathered here now,
will you take them along too?
ありがとうね！
Thank you!
よーし！
Alright!
じゃあそろそろ次の曲いっちゃおっかな！
Now, shall we move on to the next song?!
でもさっきので結構MP使ったけど大丈夫そう？マジックポイント。
But we used quite a bit of MP just now, are we okay? Magic points.
まだまだいけますよ！
We can still keep going!
いけるよ！
We can!
オッケー、じゃあこの後も楽しんでいってください！
Okay, then please enjoy the rest of the show too!
それでは次の曲、いっちょの召喚！
Now, for the next song, a joint summoning!
レッツゴー！楽しんでね！
Let's go! Enjoy yourselves!
悪戯に君をずっと見ていた訳じゃない
It's not like I've been watching you playfully all along.
僕の考えを当ててご覧よ
Try guessing what I'm thinking.
些細な仕草 視線 瞬き
Trifling gestures, glances, blinks—
君はもう掌に
you're already in the palm of my hand.
剥き出しのtrapなんてかかる訳ないわ
There's no way I'd fall for such an obvious trap.
甘い言葉にも惑わされない
I won't be swayed by sweet words either.
心の奥の奥の奥まで見透かしちゃうよ
I'll see straight through to the very depths of your heart.
(looking thinking touching feeling,)
why you know?
i know it
(looking thinking touching feeling,)
understand?
(meaning, meaning of love)
“are you ready?”
自覚ないでしょうね思い通りに
You're probably unaware, but exactly as I planned,
君は動かされている事！
you are being made to move!
単純じゃないの駆け引きのhintを全て見落とさないで
Don't overlook a single hint in this complex game of wits.
(meaning of love, meaning of love)
加速してく
Accelerating,
(meaning of love, meaning of love)
二人の鼓動
our two heartbeats.
(meaning of love, meaning of love)
心理戦は次のstageへ
The psychological battle moves to the next stage.
虚ろなその目に私はどう映るの
How do I reflect in those hollow eyes?
とても煌めきびでまるでcinderella
So dazzling, just like Cinderella.
突き刺さる視線ズキンと感じて君に余裕見せつけて
Feeling a piercing gaze throb, showing off your composure,
あからさま過ぎてお腹がよじれるよ
it's so blatant it makes my stomach twist.
既に君はもう出来上がっている頭で次の次の次まで見通しなくち
You're already all set; you've gotta see way ahead into the future.
(looking thinking touching feeling,)
why you know?
i know it
(looking thinking touching feeling,)
understand?
(meaning, meaning of love)
“are you ready?”
唯一無二のjoker手にする為に
To make the one and only Joker yours,
欲望を露わにしているほど
the more you bare your desires, the more...
らりぱっぱらぱっぱらっぱ
Rari pappara papparappa
純粋が仇になる世界で
In a world where purity is a liability,
Are you ready?
唯一無二のジョーク手にするために
Just to make a unique joke all my own,
欲望をさらけ出してる本当
Baring my desires for all to see...
離れてく世界のロジックを
The logic of a world drifting further away—
君は楽しんでるかい?
Are you enjoying it?
重要な鍵は
The crucial key
隠されたシークレット
Is a hidden secret.
後戻りできないステージへ
To a stage of no return!
気づいてるでしょ ここにいる意味さえも
You must realize the meaning of being here,
秘札はそれぞれ 互いの手札に
Each holding our trump cards in our hands.
頭と心で暴き出して 胸を打ち抜け
Uncovering it with mind and heart, shoot right through my chest!
自覚ないでしょ ねぇ 思い通りに
You aren't even aware, are you? Just as you wish,
君は動かされていること
You are being manipulated.
単純じゃないの かけ引きのヒットを 全部拾って
It's not so simple—catching every hit in our game of tug-of-war,
唯一無二のジョーク手にすることで
By making this one-of-a-kind joke your own,
理解できた愛の形を
You were able to understand the shape of love,
どこかの誰かに仕えられていても
Even if it was arranged by someone somewhere.
最後に笑う君と
With you, who will have the last laugh,
加速してく
Accelerating further!
ふたりの孤独 真実(しんじつ)は月のステージへ
The two of us in solitude—truth leads to the lunar stage!
だから ここから未来へ
So, from here toward the future!
ござる ござる なんでもござると
Gozaru, gozaru, whatever it is, gozaru!
きりりづけ ごめんのマジカルワールド
Sharp and poised, sorry, it's a magical world!
M・A・G・I・C 魔法の呪文 M・A・G・I・C 魔法少女ござるネット！
M-A-G-I-C magical spell! M-A-G-I-C, Magical Girl Gozaru Net!
ござる ござる 連投
Gozaru, gozaru, posting consecutively!
頭が覚めたら 時刻寸前 お気に入りのワラジを履いたなら かけぬけるアジリティ
Once my mind wakes up, it's just in time! Putting on my favorite sandals, agility rushing through!
ノートでジャキンジャキン ゲストマジカルは男から見てもまほほ... しょぼちょまり?
Notebook goes jakin-jakin! Guest magical looks pretty impressive even to guys... wait, shobo-chomari?
どこから見ても魔法 少女しょぼまり 日々ふせものども
No matter where you look, it's magic! A slightly pitiful magical girl, daily crouching down with others.
日々ごこうやつ 悪代官ずたち 外とかわいい だいぶかわいい
Hibi goukou yatsu akudaikan zutachi soto to kawaii daibu kawaii
召しゃのワンドのサンディになるでござる まじかるわんどきり
Mesha no wando no sandi ni naru de gozaru majikaru wando kiri
ござる ござる うちりでござる
Gozaru, gozaru, it's inside gozaru!
まじかるなみだうちを おみまいするでござる
Giving you a magical tearful blow, de gozaru!
ござる ござる この世界を守る
Gozaru, gozaru, protecting this world!
炭で君 カレんな 姿 ごらんあれ 魔法少女ましかるでござる
Sumi de kimi karen na sugata goran are magical girl gozaru!
ふりふりひらひら 強風に舞う
Frilly and fluttering, dancing in the strong wind!
袴の裾をちゃんとつまんで決めるポーズ
Tucking up the hem of my hakama and striking a pose!
ござる ござる 闇のちでござる 魔法少女しょぼまり
Gozaru, gozaru, it's the power of darkness, magical girl shobomari!
秘密こそ至上の 天下無敵でござる
Secrets are supreme, invincible de gozaru!
ござる ござる 闇討ちでござる
Gozaru, gozaru, a surprise attack de gozaru!
魔法少女はスバレ どたかようじでござる
Magical girls are subaru, dotaka youji de gozaru!
ござる ござる この世界を守る
Gozaru, gozaru, protecting this world!
魔法の国から おしのびで迷い出た
Sneaking out from the magical realm, I wandered in!
謎の勉強もさせい 魔法少女ましかるでござる
Making me study mysterious things, magical girl gozaru!
そんなふうに素敵を つくりたい
I want to create wonderful things like that!
「かわいくありたい」と願う
I wish to be cute,
忘れちゃいけない魔法 守りたいゴザル
and never forget the magic I want to protect, gozaru!
ゴザル ゴザレ いつまでもゴザル
Gozaru, gozare, always gozaru!
胸きゅんな一撃をお見舞いするでゴザル
Delivering a heart-pounding strike, gozaru!
ゴザル ゴザレ この世界を守る
Gozaru, gozare, protect this world,
完璧に綺麗な姿 ご覧あれ
behold my flawlessly pristine figure!
マジカルゴザル
Magical girl Machikaru, gozaru!
IMD! IMD! 魔法の呪文 IMD! マジかるゴザル Let's go!
IMD! IMD! The magic spell, IMD! Magical gozaru, let's go!
つまんない日常を捨てて 奇抜が照るんでしょ この人生
Toss away the boring routine, eccentricity lights up this life, right?
What's me do? ひとつ残らず沈む街
What's me do? A city sinking down without a single thing left.
泡なき日 突き放すミラージュ
On days without bubbles, a cold, rejecting mirage.
平穏な ちょっと宇宙まで
To a peaceful, slightly distant cosmos—
秒針は 音を立てて 夜を急かす 魔物のように
The second hand ticks away, rushing the night like a monster.
人生は 一瞬にして 溶ける魔法 恐れんなら 駆け抜けて 思い通り
Life is magic that melts in an instant; if you're afraid, dash through it just as you wish!
お洒落な場所飛び乗るゼップライビング あたしは大変シンメトリー
Zepp-riding into stylish places, I am thoroughly symmetrical!
散らぐね 待て 堪忍 さよなら グッバイ レトルト感 いつかはカオス クラップをどうぞ プライベートな妄想バレ
Scattering, waiting, bearing it, farewell, goodbye, a retort feel; someday chaos, please give a clap, private delusions exposed!
ビビデ バビデ ブー わん びびで ばびで ぶー わん
Bibidi babidi boo wan, bibide babide bu wan!
ごちゃがたってもしょうがないから 修羅場をとぶらい
It can't be helped if it's messy, so let's jump into the battlefield!
ビビデ バビデ ブー わん びびで ばびで ぶー わん 今夜にあっとならぶ 寝坊中によっても勝ちでしょう
Bibidi babidi boo wan, bibide babide bu wan! Tonight, even if we oversleep lined up surprisingly, we win!
だだだだ ダンス ラリラリホ どんな問題も 会話一つ 拍手も 正解も 間違いも 愛す本当の私の理想
Dada-da-da dance, rarirariho! Every problem solved with a single conversation, applause, correct answers, mistakes—I love my true ideal.
荒んだ世界は 見解の 見解がして 踊るためじゃ 安心じゃ 心配 歩みすぐ ジャンプイン ジャンプイン ナウ
A desolate world, views diverging, dancing for peace of mind, no, worries—step right up, jump in, jump in now!
ちぎちぎばんだ ちぎばんだ いとだくにき いかだくに日に ぎりぎりばっぱ 君たた今 ハプニング しちまおう
Tearing and binding, close calls day by day, right on the edge—let's make it happen right now!
まだまだ ビビったんじゃ 寂しに乱射 一発じゃ 打ち足りないわ 遂に導き出した 君にアンサー ハイになるまで踊ってよ
Still scared? Random shots out of loneliness aren't enough. The answer I finally reached for you: dance until you get high!
ビビデ バビデ ブー わん びびで ばびで ぶー わん
Bibidi babidi boo wan, bibide babide bu wan!
お洒落な場所飛び乗るゼップライビング あたしは大変シンメトリー
Zepp-riding into stylish places, I am thoroughly symmetrical!
散らぐね 待て 堪忍 さよなら グッバイ レトルト感 いつかはカオス クラップをどうぞ プライベートな妄想バレ
Scattering, waiting, bearing it, farewell, goodbye, a retort feel; someday chaos, please give a clap, private delusions exposed!
ビビデ バビデ ブー わん びびで ばびで ぶー わん
Bibidi babidi boo wan, bibide babide bu wan!
ごちゃがたってもしょうがないから 修羅場をとぶらい
It can't be helped if it's messy, so let's jump into the battlefield!
ビビデ バビデ ブー わん びびで ばびで ぶー わん 今夜にあっとならぶ 寝坊中によっても勝ちでしょう
Bibidi babidi boo wan, bibide babide bu wan! Tonight, even if we oversleep lined up surprisingly, we win!
ハッ ここはどこ？ 私はポルカ
Ha! Where is this? I'm Polka.
車にねられて… 気づいたら知らない人たちに囲まれている
Hit by a car... and before I knew it, I was surrounded by strangers!
これっていわゆる異世界転移！？
Is this what they call being transported to another world?!
なんでこっちに剣を向けてんですか？ 何だかんだ大ピンチ！
Why are you pointing your swords at me? Total big pinch no matter how you look at it!
とりあえず にげろ～！
Run away for now!
冒険の経のウェイト どうすれば 歌って踊れば きっと大丈夫
The weight of the adventure's sutra—what should we do? If we sing and dance, it'll surely be fine!
さあ 集め殺到の君も 牙のすごい君も Raise your hands! アガっちゃえ
Now, you with the surging crowd, you with the amazing fangs—raise your hands and get hyped!
カワイいは この世界でも共通の ラブ＆ピース
"Cute" is universal love & peace even in this world!
剣と魔法じゃ 作れない未来 今 作れそうな気がした
A future that swords and magic can't create—I feel like we can create it right now.
怖い顔しないで はいにこ
Don't make a scary face, say cheese!
怖い顔しないで
Don't make a scary face.
はいにっこり
Smile!
召喚ショーケース！
Summoning Showcase!
魔王と仲良くなった尾丸ポルカは
Omaru Polka, having befriended the Demon King,
平和条約を結ぶことに成功しました
successfully concluded a peace treaty.
剣も魔法を使うことはありませんでしたが
Though she never had to use swords or magic,
世界に平和をもたらした彼女は英雄だったのかもしれません
she who brought peace to the world might just have been a hero.
ハッピーギラファ〜！！
Happy Giraffa!
ねねちのギラギラファンミーティングへようこそ！
Welcome to Nenechi's Gira-Gira Fan Meeting!
さあ！ツノとアゴを長〜く伸ばして、
Now! Stretch out those horns and chin,
思いっきり楽しんじゃおうね！
and let's have the time of our lives!
それじゃ、いくよ〜！
Here we go!
アミー！カケー！ビバギラファ！
Awesome! Cool! Viva Giraffa!
カブクワ
Kabukuwa!
ギラギラ最高だね！カブクワ
Gira-gira is the best! Kabukuwa!
Amore Kabu-Kuwa Yeah!
カブクワ クリクリおめめラブ カブクワ
Kabukuwa, round sparkling eyes love, Kabukuwa!
Asore Kabu-Kuwa Yeah! 愛のダンスはむちむちョ
Asore Kabu-Kuwa Yeah! The dance of love is voluptuous!
飛んでシュビドゥバメロメロ
Fly and go shubiduba melomelo!
みんな集まれソロソロ Chu☆ Chu☆ Chu☆
Everyone gather around, step by step, Chu☆ Chu☆ Chu☆
パヤパヤパヤパヤ
Payapaya payapaya!
すごい！みんなのおかげで、こんなにたくさんのカブクワたちが集まってくれたよ〜！！
Amazing! Thanks to everyone, so many stag beetles have gathered here!
自分に拍手！そして、自然に拍手〜！！
Give yourselves a round of applause! And naturally, applause!
ギラファギラファギラファギラファ、強くてカッコいい
Giraffa giraffa giraffa giraffa, strong and cool!
ギラギラファンタスティックなノコギリクワガタ
Gira-gira fantastic saw stag beetle!
宝物だよ アミーー！カケーー！ビバギラファ！
It's a treasure! Awesome! Cool! Viva Giraffa!
カブクワ カブクワ
Kabukuwa! Kabukuwa!
カブクワ こんChu☆ Chu☆ パヤパヤパヤパヤ
Kabukuwa, kon-Chu☆ Chu☆ Payapaya payapaya!
パヤパヤパヤパヤ ゆっじ！
Payapaya payapaya, yucci!
さあ！じゃあこれから一緒に、特別なトレーニング、やっちゃおうかな〜？？
Now! Shall we do a special training together from here on??
足を肩幅に開いて、手を前にして
Open your feet to shoulder width, hands forward,
芝刈りパンプアップ、はじめんづよ〜！
Lawn mower pump-up, let's start!
ブーン！パリパリパリパリパリパリパリパリパリパリ…
Zoom! Pari-pari-pari-pari...
ムキムキなLove me バキバキでBurning
Buffed and loving me, ripped and burning!
燃えるカラダ、ほらね誰もかれも
Burning body, look, everyone,
振り返るでしょ？ねぇ見せ付けてやれの！
will turn around, right? Hey, show it off!
腰にはヴィーナスえくぼ やれんのか Muscle！
On your waist, Venus dimples! Can you do it, Muscle?
止まらない Work Out！
Unstoppable Work Out!
最強になりたいかァーッ！？ (Yeah〜ッ！)
Do you want to be the strongest!? (Yeah!)
ムキムキになりたいかァーッ！？ (Yeah〜ッ！)
Do you want to be buffed!? (Yeah!)
この世の全てを守り抜く、祝福が欲しいかァーッ！？ (Yeah〜ッ！)
Do you want the blessing to protect everything in this world!? (Yeah!)
やるしかないっしょ、バリバリで Work Out！
Gotta do it, high-intensity Work Out!
ノー筋肉！ノーライフ！ノー筋肉のライフ！ ノー筋肉でぴんなビーナス
No muscle! No life! No muscle no life! No muscle is a fine Venus!
ノー筋肉！ノーライフ！ノー筋肉のライフ！
No muscle! No life! No muscle no life!
お隣さんもマッチョマッチョ！
Your neighbor is macho macho!
ノー筋肉！ノーライフ！ノー筋肉のライフ！ やる気ホンキ大好き♡ ノー筋肉！
No muscle! No life! No muscle no life! Motivation, earnestness, I love it! No muscle!
ノー筋肉！ノーライフ！ノー筋肉のライフ！ 頑張るキミとマッチョマッチョ！
No muscle! No life! No muscle no life! You doing your best and macho macho!
Yeah! マッチョ！
Yeah! Macho!
がぉってこ がぉってこ がぉってこ がぉってこ
Gaotteko, gaotteko, gaotteko, gaotteko
きみのがおが聴こえると そんな日もちょっとやさしくなる
When I hear your roar, even days like that become a little kinder.
おすそわけしたくて 踊って踊って踊ってんだ
Wanting to share it, I dance and dance and dance.
がぉってこ がぉってこ ジャンプするなら今しかないし がぉってこ がぉってこ
Gaotteko, gaotteko, if we're gonna jump, there's no time but now, gaotteko, gaotteko
ねえ、ドクター ねえ、ドクター メンテしてよ、ドクター
Hey Doctor, hey Doctor, maintenance please, Doctor
またいつもの 例のバグ
Another usual bug again.
ハッピー＆ラッキー イケイケするモード
Happy & lucky, going all-out mode!
組み立ててマシキノココロ どこだ
Building up a machine heart, where is it?
おっかしえねえ おっかしえねえ くたらないね Yay, Yay!
That's strange, that's strange, boring, Yay, Yay!
わけないね わけないね ハイスペックなんだ
No way, no way, it's high-spec!
最先端のポーン やらなきゃ損
The state-of-the-art pawn, you lose out if you don't.
時々が止まりそうねじまいって
Sometimes it feels like time is stopping, winding up the screw,
なんてゆーか Everyday ねじまいてねじまいてよ
What can I say? Everyday, wind it up, wind it up!
ちょっとだけね ちょっとちょっとだけね
Just a little bit, just, just a little bit,
一歩パッポ鳴らして 夢を作る
Making a step, sound it out, creating dreams!
ちょっとだけね ちょっとだけね でもちょっとだけじゃ
Just a little bit, just a little bit, but just a little bit...
そのうち 足らなくなるかも
Before long, it might not be enough!
ねえ、ドクター メンテしたの、ドクター
Hey, Doctor, did you maintain it, Doctor?
手がわからん 手がわからん 分かんないラララララ
Don't know what to do, clueless, lalalala.
次元ノ呪いなんて払おう
Let's exorcise dimensional curses!
なんたっかおっかないね おっかないね とんでもないね Yay, Yay!
Somehow it's scary, unbelievable, Yay, Yay!
これはもうテクノロジーだ
This is already technology!
三原則だって握ってるもん
We've even got the three laws in our hands.
分かったらその手ですぐ巻いて
Once you understand, wind it up right away with that hand!
やんちゃっても笑って ねじまいてねじまいてよ
Even if it's mischievous, laugh and wind it up!
ちょっとだけね ちょっとちょっとだけね
Just a little bit, just, just a little bit,
君がにしても笑わせてあせる
Even if you do that, make them laugh and rush!
ちょっとだけね ちょっとだけね
Just a little bit, just a little bit,
ほらキラキラテキラキラ アイデンティティアップデートして
Look, sparkly, update your identity!
どうもありがとう そこからが
Thank you very much, from there onwards...
ピッポパッポ ピッポパッポ ピッカしっかり
Pippo-papppo, glittering and solid,
シャンゼ 起きて起きて 天気羊
Shanse, wake up, wake up, weather sheep,
ごっちらにきやシャンゼ
Over here, you see, Shanse,
その前にひとまずねじまいって
wind it up for now before that!
なんてゆーか Everyday ねじまいてねじまいてよ
What can I say? Everyday, wind it up, wind it up!
ちょっとだけね ちょっとちょっとだけね
Just a little bit, just, just a little bit,
おだね 夢を作る
Creating dreams,
ちょっとだけね ほんのちょっとだけね
Just a little bit, just a little bit,
盗撮でもなんでもいいけど明日もちょっとだけ
Stalking or whatever is fine, but tomorrow too, just a little bit
巻いて ちょっとだけね ちょっとちょっとだけね
wind it... just a little bit, just, just a little bit,
こんな毎日も悪くないよ
Even days like this everyday aren't bad!
ちょっとだけね ちょっとちょっとだけね
Just a little bit, just, just a little bit,
でもちょっとだけじゃそのうち足りなくなるかも
But just a little bit might not be enough before long!
ピッポパッポ ピッポパッポ ピッカしっかり
Pippo-papppo...
シャンゼ 起きて起きて 天気羊
Shanse...
ごっちらにきやシャンゼ
Over here...
Intersection
[Title: Intersection]
おぼれたいな 愛がぎゅっと
I want to drown, love tightly squeezing in,
ハマる君の口車で
caught up in your smooth talk.
変わりたいな 気持ちもっと
I want to change, my feelings even more,
声を出して 叫びたいね
raising my voice, I want to shout out!
ネオンのまぶしい夜じゃ
In nights blinded by neon lights,
行くよすぐ去って
I'm leaving right away, heading out.
薄暗いドアの向こう側
On the other side of the dim door,
決壊した
it has collapsed.
君の太陽を探しては
Searching for your sun,
アルコールで振り付けたフロア
a floor choreographed with alcohol.
この出汁で出るが調節するように
Adjusting so that it comes out naturally with this broth,
気にしないでなんて言わないで
Don't say "don't worry about it,"
本当はいつも正直じゃないけど
truth is, I'm not always honest, but
気づいてよなんて言えなくて
unable to say "notice me,"
嘘ばっかり
it's all lies.
おぼれたいな 愛がぎゅっと
I want to drown, love tightly squeezing in,
ハマる君の口車で
caught up in your smooth talk.
変わりたいな 気持ちもっと
I want to change, my feelings even more,
ずっと飲み干すから
because I'll drink it all down forever.
認めたいな I wannaグッと
Uncontainable dreams held in both hands,
かなりギリのツカデンの
growing up, I find myself reminiscing.
変わりたいな 気持ちもっと
Look at me, worrying over the little things,
家をチョイアブないで
what would my past self say?
(始まるストーリー) さあ 旅 に 出 よう
Riding on the wind wrapping around the streets,
点滅と減滅の間 永遠と快楽の狭間
let's start our journey!
言えない夜想曲 まだない夜の切な思い
Starring star, in the blink of an eye,
白黒すぐ塗りつぶし 今日真っ赤かに染めてどうした
a miraculous night unfolds,
そんなに急かさんでよほらほら ぐるぐる巡ってくクルクル 黒黒いったりきたり不退転
holding onto something precious in my heart.
くるくるぐるぐる廻っていく
Starring star, stumbling and falling stars,
のんびりぐらりもいいじゃないけど
gathering them up,
言えない秘密と言い訳はえて
I thought maybe I could be a bit stronger than before.
耳の奥そこで繰り返しイヤフォンでききあきた曲が
It shines brighter than back when I was covered in sweat,
そのリピートと交代するように
but there are no lies in who I am now.
気にしないでなんて言わないで本当はいつも正直じゃないけど
Running up the small hill and looking down at the town,
気が付いてよなんて言えなくて
singing in search of tomorrow.
そればっかり 溺れたいなアイガジャギュッと
Starring star, in the blink of an eye,
ハマる君の草でん かわいいたいな気持もっと
a miraculous night unfolds,
ブルーの身細いからだ
holding onto something precious in my heart.
認めたいな I wanna グッとかなりギリのツカデンの
Starring star, fluttering and descending stars,
変わりたいな 気持ちもっと家をチョイアブないで
if we cross paths once more,
(始まるストーリー)さあ旅に出よう
I thought I could be a little stronger than today.
あんしんまり もっとまり
Always by my side, stay closer to me,
あいして
I love you so much!
むぐろビーツ しーごのビーツ
Muglo beats, ultimate beats,
muglo beats, ultimate beats.
むぐろビーツ しーごのビーツ しぇけなビーツ
Muglo beats, ultimate beats, shake beats,
むぐろでびーつ
muglo's dead beats.
死んじゃったらご出世 あの世でビーツ
If you die, you'll be reincarnated in another world's beats,
でも存外楽しい 地獄でピースピースピース
but staying alive is fun too, peace, peace, peace!
もうくよくよしないで
Don't say things like "I want to die,"
ほら高い高い跳躍できる
hey, look how high and high I can jump!
切り替えてGo Dance Dance
Switching over to dance, dance,
チュウチュウむぐろ単身単身チュウチュウチュウ
choo-choo, muglo, single, single, choo-choo-choo,
キスでチュウチュウチュウ
kiss with choo-choo-choo,
でもベッドはチュウチュウチュウ
but bed is choo-choo-choo!
ビーツに魔チュウチュウ あまずっぱいチュウチュウチュウ
beats to the chuchu, sour to the chuchu,
Do the ハリラドゥー Do the 注射でバッドなユースアロハ
dance, Harada, dance, inject the better us all over!
踊ろうおどろしい 君たちと踊る踊る
Dance and be amazed, dancing with you,
無限ハッピーハッピーエブリバディ
infinite happy, happy everybody!
それっていいんじゃない? 愛したいし誰からも愛されたいのって
Isn't it great? I want to love and be loved
良くないの? いけないの?
by everyone!
ありあまる不義理だっても許してね
Forgive me for being a bit too greedy!
契約わかったら返事
Contract? Let me know if you understand!
感動しました投げました 地獄最高！
I was moved, I threw myself, hell is the best!
むぐろビーツ しーごのビーツ
Muglo beats, ultimate beats,
muglo beats, ultimate beats.
あっちとそっちで寂しいですか？
Are you lonely with just the two of us?
ボディーガードがいるでしょう？
There must be a bodyguard, right?
むぐろビーツ しーごのビーツ
Muglo beats, ultimate beats,
誰がクックロビン Ai, ai, aye!
who's the cucklo bean? Aye, aye, aye!
待って どうせこの世なんて
Wait, why are we talking about the afterlife?
待って みなとのひとつ
Wait, we're all in the same boat!
ねえ 待って とおりすぎてく
Hey, wait, we're just passing through,
だけなの?
what's the point?
ねえ 待ってって言ってんでしょ！
Hey, I said "wait"!
いたってのりのり
Let's just ride along.
キュートがこうじて減らした悪意の根拠なく無敵なタキラセボディを
Cute-to-the-core, reducing malice with no mercy,
こっそりそせチュウチュウ なんて正義なチュチュチュ
sneaking in chuchu, what a righteous chuchu!
わるさがおみたく窓を叩くから帰れないでオルベ！
We're smashing windows like bad girls, so we can't go home!
断然ほっとのむチュチュ ハートビートはイェレチュウ
Completely calm chuchu, heartbeat is yeredu!
ショーワ かなりショーワ
Is it shocking? Quite shocking!
しゃべればよさろ Beautiful, beautiful day!
If we keep chatting, it'll be a beautiful, beautiful day,
うつしくわらおう笑おう えいと握手してぎゅっとして ここってパラダイス
smiling, laughing, hugging, and getting cozy, what a paradise!
みんな好き好き何にもかも手に入れたいです
I want everyone to take everything in, and love it all!
さつナチュラル ポケモン
That's just natural, Pokewoman!
ごめんビジーは死んでも治りません
Even if my beauty fades, I won't recover!
ドンドンの荒れ地
The unending rough waves,
ケラケラケラドゲ脱出
shaking, rocking, and breaking out of hell!
地獄王化 ゲラゲラゲラドゲ脱出ケラケラケラ
The ultimate kings escape, escape, escape, escape!
ラッタタリホウ 月日と踊れや踊れ
Rat-a-tat-ri-ho, dance through the days and nights!
頬杖ついて歌えば風が吹く
Rest your chin on your hand and sing, and the wind will blow.
ラッタタリホウ みんなまだまだ上がるんだ
Rat-a-tat-ri-ho, everyone's still climbing higher!
大海小海を書き分けて出航！
Parting the great and small seas, set sail!
アイアイマール
Aye-aye, mate!
でも元々ちゅっちゅっ
But originally, muah muah,
遊び散らかしてラッタタリホウ
playing around messily, rat-a-tat-ri-ho.
アイアイマール
Aye-aye, mate!
さばけそこがアンダーウォーターなんだわ良い旅を
Deal with it, right there is underwater, have a good trip.
踊りましたらば椋鳥に花束を
If we danced, a bouquet to the starling.
踊ろう踊ろうしっ！君たちと踊ろう踊ろう
Let's dance, dance, shh! Let's dance and dance with you all!
抜け駆けハッピーハッピーエビバデ それでもいいんじゃない？
Sneaking out, happy happy everybody, isn't that still fine?
みんな大好き大好き頂戴してる
Receiving everyone's love and adoration.
それって良くないの？いけないの？
Is that no good? Is it forbidden?
契約成立
Contract established!
分かったら返事ね
Answer me once you understand!
はーい！というわけで、7曲連続でお送りしまして
Ha-i! And so, we've delivered seven songs in a row—
待って、まだ7曲じゃないでしょ？歩くここまではね
Wait, wasn't it seven songs yet? Walking up to here, right?
振り返ってみましょう！
Let's look back on them!
7曲ですよ、7曲です、皆さん！サスペクト！
Seven songs, seven songs, everyone! Suspect!
よし、久しぶりだ、そう。久しぶりに歌ったよね、これ
Alright, it's been a while, yeah. We sang this after a long time, right?
よかったね。でもこの曲だからね
That was great. But because it's this song—
でも踊りもかっこよかったよね。だ、だ、でしょ？
But the dance was cool too. Ri-, right, right?
そしてねねの魔法少女マジカルゴザルじゃきーん！
And Nene's magical girl Magical Gozaru, ja-kiin!
いや、よかったわ。
Man, that was great.
はい、ポルカビビデバブをやりました。
Yes, Polka did Bibbidi-Bobbidi-Boo.
いいじゃん。ビビデバブー。ありがとうございます。
That's great. Bibbidi-Bobbidi-Boo. Thank you very much!
そしてメドレー。わらのねオリ曲メドレーみたいな感じになってて
And the medley. It felt like a medley of Wara's original songs—
忙しかったけど楽しかった！
It was busy, but fun!
最後パリパリなのまずいよね。
Ending on crispy/crackling was bad, right?
最後パリパリじゃないか。違う違う、最後ガオってことだよ。
Wait, isn't it crispy? No, no, ending with "Gao!"
ガオってんだろ、お前。もうさっきの記憶なくなってんじゃん、お前！
"Gao", you say? You've already lost your memory from earlier, you!
間違っちゃった！でそのあとが
I got it wrong! And after that was—
はい、リリビビですね。よかったよ。
Right, Lili-Bibi. It was great.
あってたよ、すごい。お互い交差する、あずきちの曲ですけど、名曲の中での、一番好きな曲、最高だね。
It was correct, amazing. Azuki's song where you cross paths, among masterpieces, it's your favorite song, absolutely the best.
最高や。そして
Absolute peak. And—
曲がり曲がで、好き好き大好き超愛してる。
Magari-magara, I love love love you so much.
よかったよ、ちょ難しかったね。
It was great, it was a bit difficult though.
本当に難しかったね、船長。
It was truly difficult, Captain.
船長って歌が上手なんだなってすごく思いました。
I really thought the Captain is so good at singing.
改めて先輩たちへの尊敬が生まれます。レスペクト、レスペクト。
It gives me renewed respect for our seniors. Respect, respect.
歌わせていただいてありがとうございます。ありがとうございました。
Thank you for letting us sing it. Thank you very much!
ということでここからは嬉しいお知らせとなります！
And with that, from here on we have a happy announcement!
こちらをご覧ください！どうぞ！
Please take a look at this! Here you go!
ネポラボ記念グッズ発売告知となります！
This is the announcement for the NePoLaBo anniversary merchandise release!
こちらイラストですね、にもし先生に描いていただきました！
This illustration was drawn for us by Nimoshi-sensei!
今回は天体パレードという大テーマがありまして、私たちネポラボは占星術師をテーマに描いていただきました。ありがとうございます！
This time, the grand theme is "Celestial Parade", and we had us NePoLaBo drawn with an astrologer theme. Thank you very much!
かわいいね。ちょっとセクシーじゃない？
It's cute. Isn't it a bit sexy?
それではですね、詳細を見ていきましょう。まずは、こちら！
Now then, let's look at the details. First, this one!
プレミアムアクリル色紙です、こちら。
It's the Premium Acrylic Shikishi board, right here.
イラストがすごくきれいに見えて、あと複製サインとかがついているので、これめちゃくちゃ豪華で綺麗ですよ。綺麗よ！綺麗だよ！
The illustration looks super clean, and it comes with duplicated signatures, so this is crazy luxurious and gorgeous. Gorgeous! Gorgeous!
続いて、こちら！アクリルスタンド！
Moving on, this one! Acrylic stands!
台座付きのね、豪華なアクリルスタンドとなっておりまして、大きさは15センチ程度を予想しております。
They are gorgeous acrylic stands with bases, and we estimate them to be around 15 centimeters.
式士とは異なる表情になっているので、いろんなところで楽しめます。
They have different expressions from the shikishi, so you can enjoy them in various places.
続いては、こちら！
Next is this one!
缶バッジセットでございます！
It's the Can Badge Set!
こちらもね、たちの表情が楽しめる缶バッジセットとなっております！
This is also a can badge set where you can enjoy everyone's expressions!
そして続いては、こちら！
And next is this one!
鍵モチーフキーホルダー！こちら配信でも持っている、あの杖をイメージした鍵モチーフ...
Key-motif keyholders! Imagining the staff we hold during the stream, key-motif...
鍵モチーフキーホルダーとなっております。
These are key-motif keychains.
4種とも違うの色が異なる、右上に小さなビジューがついてます。
All 4 have different colors, with a small jewel on the top right.
かわいい！
Cute!
おしゃれ！ほしい！
Stylish! I want them!
そして続いては、こちら！コレクションBOXでございます！
And next is this! The collection box!
なにこれ！すごい！
What's this! Amazing!
もうなんか本型ボックスに、よりぬきの鍵モチーフキーホルダーがセットになった、そんな感じになっております！
It's a book-shaped box containing a set of selected key-motif keychains!
表紙はもちろん、背表紙や裏表紙のデザインもこだわった、満足感たっぷりのボックスでございます！
The cover, spine, and back cover designs are carefully crafted for a satisfying box!
ええ、買ってね！買ってね！
Buy it! Buy it!
さて、そしてさらにですね、おしらせがあります。
Now, and furthermore, we have an announcement.
なんですか？
What is it?
なんとこちらです！
It's this!
おっ！なにこれ！なにこれ！
Oh! What's this? What's this?
ネポラボの新曲、「メロゾーマ」がこのあと、
Nepolabo's new song, "Melozoma,"
24時18日の、0時からデジタルリリース！
will be digitally released at midnight on the 18th!
やったー！
Yay!
「メロゾーマ」ってなんだ？なんだ？「メロゾーマ」って！
What is "Melozoma"? What on earth is "Melozoma"!
このあと新曲を披露しますので、絶対聞いてください！
We'll perform the new song right after this, so be sure to listen!
いやー買ったぞどうも！メロゾーマだな？ネポラボめ！ネポラボめ！
Bought it! Hello, Nepolabo? Darn Nepolabo! Darn Nepolabo!
そしてですね、我ら5期生周年ということで、各個人のチャンネルにてMVがアップされておりますのでぜひチェックしてみてください！
And also, as it's our 5th generation anniversary, MVs have been uploaded to each person's channel, so please check them out!
こちらラミィが「コズミックワンダフルツアー」を上げておりまして、
Here, Lamy uploaded "Cosmic Wonderful Tour,"
ネネはハイパージャンピー！
Nene uploaded "Hyper Jumpy,"
ポルカはトゥインクルフォールを上げてます。
Polka uploaded "Twinkle Fall."
ぜひ見てください！
Please check them out!
じゃあ個人の告知いくか。
Shall we move on to individual announcements?
はい、そうですね。
Yes, that's right.
えとラミィが8月15日に発売したファーストアルバム「Fleur de neige」が予約受付中となっております。
Lamy's 1st album "Fleur de neige", released on August 15th, is available for pre-order.
おめでとう！
Congratulations!
ネネはオリジナル曲の「ごきげんドリンクバー」のMVが出ております。
Nene's original song "Gokigen Drink Bar" MV is out.
あとソロライブの配信チケット、まだ販売中なのでぜひチェックよろしくです！
And solo live streaming tickets are still on sale, so be sure to check them out!
え、ポルカです。ポルカの3周年記念のフルアニメーションMVが出ました。
Polka here. Polka's 3rd anniversary full animation MV is out.
みんないっぱい見てね！
Everyone, please watch it a lot!
そして白銀はですね、個人周年グッズ発売中でございますので、ぜひ手に入れて見てください。
And Shirogane's personal anniversary goods are currently on sale, so please get your hands on them.
そしてですね、あの私誕生日が9月なので、そろそろね、あの誕生日の告知も後々発表できると思いますので、ぜひはいTwitterなり私のチャンネルなりチェックしてみてください！
And since my birthday is in September, I think I'll be able to announce my birthday info soon, so please check my Twitter or channel!
と言うわけで、以上ネポラボアニバーサリーグッズ情報とリリース情報でした！
And that concludes the Nepolabo anniversary goods and release info!
おめでとうございます！
Congratulations!
はい、というわけでいよいよライブのクライマックス！
And now, finally, the climax of the live!
ラストもあさっきの新曲を踊って、歌って、やりたいと思います！
For the finale, we'd like to dance and sing the new song from earlier!
みんなメロゾーマになる気持ちは？
Are you ready to become Melozoma?
メロゾーマだ！
It's Melozoma!
メロゾーマ、みんなコメントの準備もちょっとしてほしいな。メロゾーマなんで。
Melozoma, everyone please get ready in the comments too, because it's Melozoma.
そしてラストはマドーゴンドラに乗って歌います！
And finally, we'll sing riding in a magic gondola!
なんかマドーゴンドラって？
What's a magic gondola?
みんな準備いいですか？
Is everyone ready?
準備しなきゃ！
We gotta get ready!
みんなメロゾーマ準備して！メロゾーマね！
Everyone, get ready for Melozoma! Melozoma, okay!
じゃあこれはメロゾーマもこれ極大魔法か？
So is this Melozoma also a ultimate magic?
でかそうね！でかそうだよね！でかデカ魔法だよ！
Looks huge! Sounds huge! It's super huge magic!
上からゴンドラが降りてくるので、みんなで一緒にメロゾーマって歌って、こちはしゃべるでいいか。オッケー！
A gondola comes down from above, so let's all sing "Melozoma" together, and we can talk. Okay!
じゃあ行くぞ！
Here we go!
せーの、メロゾーマ！！
Ready, go, Melozoma!!
おきました！
It came down!
え、これ乗れる？
Can we ride this?
乗れますかね？乗れますか？
Can we ride it? Can we?
乗れますか？乗れます！
Can we? Yes!
はーい、ついてください！
Alright, follow us!
じゃあね、みなさん最後まで盛り上がっていきましょう！
Alright everyone, let's get hyped to the very end!
じゃあ曲名もう一回言っちゃう？
Shall we say the song title again?
じゃあ、みなさん聞いてください。せーの！メロゾーマ！
Alright everyone, please listen. Ready, go! Melozoma!
とろけちゃってラビュずーっとずーっと
Melt away, love you, on and on and on,
頭の中ハートいっぱいになって
With hearts filling up my head,
ほらもっともっと釘付けになれ#めろぞーま
Look, get even more hooked on #Melozoma.
女の子は魔法使い
Girls are spellcasters,
神様がくれたプレゼント
A present given by God.
恋しちゃったんだって
Falling in love, they say,
思わせぶりだって
Acting coy, they say,
必然的アウトカム！
An inevitable outcome!
甘い酸っぱいほろ苦いカラフルなポーション使い分けてキミにかけたい呪文
Using sweet, sour, bitter, colorful potions, I want to cast a spell on you.
…なんて恥ずかしい妄想が胸の中を駆け巡るギルティ！
What an embarrassing delusion racing through my chest, guilty!
だってそばにいてほしいからメロが来る呪文…#めろぞーま
Because I want you by my side, the spell that brings melo... #Melozoma.
とろけちゃってラビュずーっとずーっと
Melt away, love you, on and on and on.
とろけちゃってラビュー
Melting love...
ずっとずっと
Always and forever.
頭の中ハートいっぱいになって ほらもっともっと
My head is full of hearts, come on, even more!
釘付けになれ#めろぞーまっ
Be glued to me, #Melozoma!
ever lasting love me...
Everlasting love me...
ever lasting love you...
Everlasting love you...
女の子は魔法使い 神様がくれた悪戯
Girls are sorceresses, a mischief given by God,
恋しちゃったんだって 思わせぶりだって 必然的outcome！
falling in love, playing hard to get—inevitable outcome!
甘い 酸っぱい ほろ苦い カラフルなポーション使い分けて キミにかけたい呪文 呟くの
Using sweet, sour, bittersweet colorful potions, I murmur a spell I want to cast on you...
...なんて 恥ずかしい妄想が
...Such embarrassing delusions
胸の中を駆け巡るギルティ！
race through my heart—Guilty!
だってそばにいてほしいから
Because I want you by my side,
メロる呪文...#めろぞーまっ
a spell that charms you... #Melozoma!
とろけちゃってラビュー
Melting love...
ずっとずっと
Always and forever.
両目見つめ ハートいっぱいになって ほらもっともっと
Looking into both eyes, my heart is full, come on, even more!
溺れてしまえ#めろぞーまっ
Drown in it, #Melozoma!
解けないでとっておきの魔法
An irresistible magic that won't wear off
いつまでも私だけ見てて
Look at only me forever
とろけちゃってラビュー ずっとずっと
Melting love, always and forever
頭の中ハートいっぱいになって ほらもっともっと
My head is full of hearts, come on, even more!
釘付けになれ#めろぞーまっ
Be glued to me, #Melozoma!
こんなにもキミに恋してるから
Because I'm so in love with you,
離れたくないハギュッ
I don't want to be apart, hug!
もっともっと想い愛したい#めろぞーまっ
I want to love and be loved more and more, #Melozoma!
この魔法が絶対解けないように
So that this magic will never wear off...
呪いと同じ類かもしれないけど
Though it might be akin to a curse...
キミといつまでもとろけていたいから
Because I want to melt with you forever...
ありったけの魔力を含めて
Containing all the magical power I have...
キミと出会った瞬間から始まった このロマンスが
This romance that started the moment I met you
ソードみたいに弾くなんて辛いよ
bouncing away like a sword is so painful.
永遠になんて空想だけど願いたいのに
Even if 'forever' is just a fantasy, I want to wish for it,
そんな魔法があればいいのに切ないけど
I wish there was such magic, though it's heartbreaking...
素直になりたい#めろぞーまっ
I want to be honest... #Melozoma!
切ないけど素直になりたい#めろぞーまっ
Heartbreaking, but I want to be honest... #Melozoma!
歌いたいなラビュー ずっとずっと
I want to sing, love, always and forever...
こんなにもキミに恋してるから 離れたくないハギュッ
Because I'm so in love with you, I don't want to let go, hug!
もっともっと想い愛したい#めろぞーまっ
I want to love and be loved more and more, #Melozoma!
とろけちゃってラビュー ずっとずっと
Melting love, always and forever
頭の中ハートいっぱいになって ほらもっともっと
My head is full of hearts, come on, even more!
釘付けになれ#めろぞーまっ
Be glued to me, #Melozoma!
解けないでとっておきの魔法
An irresistible magic that won't wear off
クラクラさせてメルティ
Make me dizzy, Melty
いつまでも私だけ見てて
Look at only me forever
歌うよ#めろぞーまっ
I'll sing it, #Melozoma!
解けないでとっておきの呪文
An irresistible spell that won't be undone
ドキドキしたいのメルシー
I want my heart to race, Merci
いつまでも私を愛してね
Love me forever
歌うよ#めろぞーまっ
I'll sing it, #Melozoma!
解けないでとっておきの呪文
An irresistible spell that won't be undone
ドキドキしたいのメルシー
I want my heart to race, Merci
いつまでも私を愛してね
Love me forever
歌うよ#めろぞーまっ
I'll sing it, #Melozoma!
イチコロね#めろぞーまっ
Taken in an instant, #Melozoma!